school-time.co 2015-03-25

# Privacy Policy - Paywings 4.0 | Paywings 4.0

### Privacy Policy

**A. INTRODUCTION**

**Word from the Company**

STPL Global has a strong commitment to providing superior service to all of our customers and visitors of this web site www.stplglobal.com and other of STPL Global sites included within [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com) (collectively, the “Website”), and particularly respecting your concerns about privacy. We understand that you may have questions about how this Website collects and uses information and we have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern the Website (the “Privacy Policy”). We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Part C below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. We have organized this Privacy Policy by major processes and areas so that you can quickly link to the information of most interest to you. The bottom line is that meeting your needs and expectations form the foundation of everything we do – including protecting your privacy.

Personal information on this Website is collected by STPL Global and if after reviewing this Privacy Policy you have any questions or privacy concerns please send an e-mail to [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com)

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

STPL Global wants you to be always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.All personal information, as further described in Part B, that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. STPL Global reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will prominently post any material changes on the home page of the Website. You will be given the opportunity to opt-out.If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which STPL Global is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in Section Creating and Updating Your Personal Account and Preferences.You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Website after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to STPL Global you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you by STPL Global or by third parties, STPL Global will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent.

**Third Party Websites**

STPL Global does not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than those Internet domains that are under the control of STPL Global itself.When you are on the STPL Global Website, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you.In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to such third party sites. STPL Global is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party sites.

**Legal Issues**

This is a United States website and is subject to United States law.STPL Global will disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to STPL Global guests, visitors, associates, or property (including this Website), or to others. As mentioned above, laws related to personal identifiable information vary by country.

STPL Global may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. STPL Global may also provide information to law enforcement to protect its property and the health and safety of individuals as permitted by statute.

**B. COLLECTED INFORMATION**

**Browsing**

This Website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse the Website and request pages from our servers.This means that, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information.When you request a page from our Website, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header, JavaScript or similar technical tools, including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information.We collect such information in order to make our Website function correctly and provide you the functionality that you see on this Website, as our servers use this information to deliver to you the pages on this Website. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use our Website and how we can better tune our Website, its contents and functionality to meet your needs.

**Information We Collect**

As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information as described above in Section Browsing.In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to the services offered on the Website, utilizing online software applications or purchasing any of the products and services available on the Website, STPL Global may ask you to voluntarily supply us with certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form.It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities and/or make any purchases.If you elect to engage in these activities or make purchases, however, STPL Global may ask that you provide us personal information, defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including but not limited to your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information.

You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline this exchange of information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information.Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary.If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity or purchase, you will not be able to engage in that activity or make such a purchase.

STPL Global is the sole owner of the information it gathers on its site. STPL Global will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our Website.

When you use the Website, STPL Global or third parties authorized by STPL Global may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Website and its services.When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser (such as Netscape Navigator® or Microsoft Internet Explorer®) automatically transmits some information to STPL Global every time you access content on one of our sites. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the “Refer”), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our Website. All of this information may be collected by STPL Global and used to analyze the activity on the Website and help improve our offerings to you.

We use such data to facilitate and track your use of the Website and its services. STPL Global also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Website.

When you submit personal information to STPL Global through this Website, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which STPL Global and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of STPL Global .Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.

STPL Global has established relationships with various service providers whose services are available to you from this Website or from web sites that are linked to this Website.Typically, these providers offer services that STPL Global customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with STPL Global services and products.In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers.Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider’s web site will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this Website in conjunction with a provider’s service will be subject to this Privacy Policy.You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers often provide that they will share with STPL Global personal information collected from you. In such instances, STPL Global may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Accessing and Updating Your Personal Preferences**

At your choice, you may create a personal account containing information such as your preferred STPL Global products and interests.Creating a personal account makes it more convenient for you to make purchases by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter personal preference information. It will allow us to inform you about special offers and promotions that may be of interest to you.

You can access and review or update your personal account information on-line or you may deactivate your account by writing to [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com) . If you deactivate your personal account, the information you submitted to create the account will be deleted provided that we may retain some data, to the extent necessary, for purposes of legal compliance and in connection with your use of the Website and licensing of our products.

You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications from STPL Global or third parties) by writing STPL Global at [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com)

**Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information**

STPL Global operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. Even your registration account password is encrypted before it is sent to our computers.

STPL Global takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with our terms of service. End User License Agreement and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you use these services at your own risk.We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. STPL Global will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You the consumer are ultimately responsible for the security of your login name and password.

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential information. It is, accordingly, subject to our company’s security procedures and corporate policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. After personally identifiable information reaches STPL Global it is stored on a server with physical and electronic security features as customary in the industry, including utilization of login/password procedures and electronic firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of STPL Global All STPL Global employees are aware of our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs.

Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our offices or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on the sites covered by this Privacy Policy is processed and stored in the United States and also in other countries where STPL Global and its service providers conduct business.

**C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

**How Your Personal Information Is Used**

STPL Global collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select.We will use your e-mail address to send a confirmation and, if necessary, might use the other information to contact you for help to process the purchase or service you have selected. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users.Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, patches, special offers, and other products and services of STPL Global and selected third parties if you have so opted to receive such communications.

STPL Global may collect information about the use of the Website, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily.This information is collected in aggregate form and STPL Global may use this statistical data for internal statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

STPL Global recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Website. Without your consent, STPL Global will not communicate any information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from STPL Global or its affiliates, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Website or the products you have purchased from STPL Global Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, STPL Global will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.

**Public Announcements**

With you prior consent, STPL Global may identify you to the public as its customer and describe in a customer case study the services and solutions delivered by STPL Global to you.STPL Global may also issue one or more press releases, containing an announcement relating to of the execution and delivery of the agreements between you and STPL Global and/or the implementation of the product by you . Nothing contained in this section shall be construed as an obligation by you to disclose any of your proprietary or confidential information to any third party.In addition, you may opt-out from this Section by writing an opt-out request to STPL Global at [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com)

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

STPL Global does use the services of third parties, such as e-mail service providers, purchase and order processing merchants and marketing companies that act as independent contractors on behalf of STPL Global These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose STPL Global specifies. We do provide non-personally identifiable information to certain service providers for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us. We prohibit the sale or transfer of personal information to entities outside of the STPL Global affiliates for their use without your approval.

STPL Global may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. STPL Global may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Privacy Policy or End User License Agreement or to protect the safety of our users and the public or under confidentiality agreements with certain third parties which assist us in developing, operating and maintaining STPL Global products.

In the event that all or substantially all of STPL Global stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, STPL Global may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity. If, as a result of such a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner, you will be given choice consistent with our policy regarding notification of changes.

**Choices Available to You**

You can always choose whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information and that choicewill not prevent you from using the STPL Global Website.Please note, however, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information.

You can choose at anytime to opt out of receiving emails from STPL Global or from having your personally identifiable information shared with selected companies. If you want to opt out, you can do so by editing your preferences with respect to email or the sharing of information. If you elect to “opt out” we will not, as applicable, share your personal information with third parties or send you emails.However, we may continue to use your personal information for internal purposes, to enhance your user experience or as necessary to administer the Website or comply with applicable law.

We reserve the right to send a one-time registration confirmation email, and infrequent service alert messages to users to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use a service they have previously signed up for, regardless of email contact opt-in status. We also reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of our End User License Agreement.

STPL Global is retaining these rights because in limited cases we feel that we may need the right to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters which will be important to you.These rights do not allow us to contact you to market a new or existing service if you have asked us not to do so, and issuance of these types of communications are rare. 

**Cookies**

Our Website uses “cookie” technology. “Cookies” are short pieces of data generated by a web server that a website stores on a user’s computer.Certain pages on our Website may require the use of a cookie for purposes of keeping information you enter on multiple pages together. Cookies also enable us to customize our Website and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience with us. In addition, cookies are used to:

  * allow registered users to sign in without typing their sign in name each time.
  * measure usage of various pages on our Website to help us make our information; more pertinent to your needs and easy for you to access;
  * and provide functionality such as online orders, STPL Global services and other functionality that we believe would be of interest and value to you.

The types of cookies that we use are referred to as “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies.Session cookies are temporary and are automatically deleted once you leave the Website.Persistent cookies remain on your computer hard drive until you delete them.We do not use cookies to gather information concerning your visits to other sites, nor ascertain any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us in your dealings with STPL Global Cookies do not corrupt or damage your computer, programs, or computer files.

In addition, the service providers we use to serve and host our advertisements, and/or deliver our e-mails, use session and persistent cookies, to track the number of times the Website is accessed and whether the site was accessed from an advertisement.There are no cookies in the advertisement or e-mail.A cookie is placed on your computer only if and when you click on an advertisement or open the e-mail.The cookie generated from the advertisement or e-mail does not contain any personally identifiable information and will remain on your hard drive until you delete it.

You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so will adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality and access certain content on our Website.

    500. **PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS**

This Privacy Policy statement was last updated on JUNE 30, 2014. STPL Global has created this Privacy Policy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website, [www.stplglobal.com](http://www.stplglobal.com/). STPL Global abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. Upon reading this Privacy Policy statement, you will know:-

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Website, as such term is defined below.

2\. The organization collecting the information. 

3\. How the information is used. 

4\. With whom the information may be shared. 

5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 

6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under STPL Global control. 

7\. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the STPL Global Website coordinator by emailing [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com) or writing to us at the following address: STPL ICT Consulting Pvt Ltd,MJR Magnifique,First Floor-Unit No-3,Survey No:75 & 76,Khajaguda X Road,Raidurga Navkhalsa,Gachibowli Road,Hyderabad-500 008.

If you feel that STPL Global has not complied with the policies outlined in this privacy statement please submit a report at [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com)

STPL Global takes and addresses its users’ privacy concerns with utmost respect and attention.If you believe that there was an instance of non-compliance with this Online Privacy Policy with regard to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write or contact STPL Global at [privacy@stplglobal.com](mailto:privacy@stplglobal.com)

In your message, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the STPL Global Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly.

Please note that if you provide STPL Global with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not). STPL Global cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.
